{
    "subject": "resource/Martin_Smith_(Royal_Marines_officer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/battle",
    "object": "resource/Iraq_War",
    "human_readable": "Martin Smith fought in the Iraq War.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9550827145576477,
            "question": "What was Martin Smith's involvement in the Iraq War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9026442766189575,
            "question": "Martin Smith is known for fighting in which war?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.859494686126709,
            "question": "What is the name of the war Martin Smith fought in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7956282496452332,
            "question": "What war did Martin Smith participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.77839195728302,
            "question": "In what war did Martin Smith have a role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7653270363807678,
            "question": "Was Martin Smith involved in military conflict?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6985337734222412,
            "question": "Where did Martin Smith fight?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6831451654434204,
            "question": "In which conflict was Martin Smith a participant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6400516629219055,
            "question": "Did Martin Smith serve in the military?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5569819808006287,
            "question": "Who fought in the Iraq War?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Martin Smith fought in the Iraq War.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5664_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Martin Smith serve in the military?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5664_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which conflict was Martin Smith a participant?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5664_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Martin Smith fight?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5664_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5664_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5664_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5664_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5664_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5664_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5664_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5664_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5664_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5664_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5664_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention Martin Smith fighting in the Iraq War. Instead, it talks about Martin Smith as a correspondent for FRONTLINE reporting on events related to the Middle East and ISIS. There is no information supporting that he personally fought in the Iraq War."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context suggesting that Martin Smith fought in the Iraq War.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text describes Martin Smith as a FRONTLINE correspondent who reports on the situation in Iraq, not as someone who participated in the war.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because there's no mention of Martin Smith fighting in the Iraq War. The text only mentions him as a correspondent, interviewing various people, including President Obama and other officials, and presenting news footage from the region, but it does not imply that he participated in military action himself.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information indicates Martin Smith is a FRONTLINE correspondent, not a soldier who fought in the Iraq War.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}